[
    {
       "question":"Evelyn Glennie was the daughter of ........",
       "choice1":"Isabel Glennie",
       "choice2": "Mrs. Jones Glennie",
       "choice3": "Mrs. Katherine",
       "choice4": "Mrs. Brunt",
       "answer": 1
   
   },
   {
       "question":"Evelyn's deafness was first noticed at the age of - ",
       "choice1":"eight",
       "choice2":"ten",
       "choice3":"five",
       "choice4":"nine",
       "answer": 4
   },
   {
       "question":"Evelyn went to the Royal Academic of Music at the age of -",
       "choice1":"ten",
       "choice2": "twelve",
       "choice3": "fifteen",
       "choice4": "seventeen",
       "answer": 4
   
   },
   {
       "question":"Royal Academy of Music is situated in ..........",
       "choice1":"America",
       "choice2":"London",
       "choice3":"France",
       "choice4":"American",
       "answer": 2
   },
   {
       "question":"Evelyn was a ..........  girl.",
       "choice1":"German",
       "choice2": "Scottish",
       "choice3": "French",
       "choice4": "American",
       "answer": 2
   
   },
   {
       "question":"When was Evelyn Glennie's deafness confirmed?",
       "choice1":"At the age of 11 years",
       "choice2":"At the age of 18 years",
       "choice3":"At the age of 8 years ",
       "choice4":"At the age of 15 years",
       "answer": 1
   },
   {
       "question":"Evelyn gives free concerts in ..........",
       "choice1":"prisons and hospitals ",
       "choice2": "schools and streets",
       "choice3": "hospitals and schools",
       "choice4": "None of these",
       "answer": 1
   
   },
   
   {
       "question":"What did Ron Forbes advise Evelyn?",
       "choice1":"Forget music ",
       "choice2": "Feel music with her body",
       "choice3": "Listen to music",
       "choice4": "None of these",
       "answer": 2
   
   },
   {
       "question":"Who improved the sound quality of the pungi?",
       "choice1":"A tailor ",
       "choice2":"A farmer",
       "choice3":"A cobler",
       "choice4":"A barber",
       "answer": 4
   },
   {
       "question":"Which  instrument got the name reeded noisemaker?",
       "choice1":"Flute",
       "choice2": "Piano",
       "choice3": "Pungi",
       "choice4": "Harmonium",
       "answer": 3
   
   },
   {
       "question":"How many holes were made on the body of the pipe?",
       "choice1":"Four ",
       "choice2":"Five",
       "choice3":"Six",
       "choice4":"Seven",
       "answer": 4
   },
   {
       "question":"Who banned the playing of pungi in royal palace?",
       "choice1":"Babur",
       "choice2": "Akbar",
       "choice3": "Shahjahan",
       "choice4": "Aurangzeb",
       "answer": 4
   
   },
   {
       "question":"Where was Bismillah Khan born?",
       "choice1":"Buxar",
       "choice2":"Dumraon",
       "choice3":"Mathura",
       "choice4":"Allahabad",
       "answer": 2
   },
   {
       "question":"Bismillah Khan's maternal uncle was-",
       "choice1":"Jahangir",
       "choice2": "Salim Khan",
       "choice3": "Ali Bux",
       "choice4": "Aurangzeb",
       "answer": 3
   
   },
   {
       "question":"Bismillah Khan was deeply attached to ",
       "choice1":"The Sutlej",
       "choice2":"The Ganga",
       "choice3":"The Narmada",
       "choice4":"The Godavari",
       "answer": 2
   },
   {
       "question":"Bismillah was born on ............",
       "choice1":"21st March 1916",
       "choice2": "21st March 1919",
       "choice3": "30th October 1917",
       "choice4": "2nd October 1905",
       "answer": 1
   
   },
   {
       "question":"Which highest Civilian Award (in 2001) did Bismillah Khan receive?",
       "choice1":"Gallantery Award",
       "choice2":"The Dronacharya Award",
       "choice3":"The Bharat Ratna",
       "choice4":"The Arjuna Award",
       "answer": 3
   },
   {
       "question":"Bismillah Khan used to sing ............ as a child.",
       "choice1":"film song",
       "choice2": "the Bhojpuri chaita",
       "choice3": "Koras",
       "choice4": "Countryside song",
       "answer": 2
   
   },
   {
       "question":"Who is Bismillah Khan?",
       "choice1":"Cricketer",
       "choice2":"Musician",
       "choice3":"Singer",
       "choice4":"Shehnai player",
       "answer": 4
   },
   {
    "question": "Shehnai was named by a ...........  .",
    "choice1":"Goldsmith",
    "choice2":"Carpenter",
    "choice3":"Barber",
    "choice4":"Cobbler",
    "answer":3
   }
   
   
   ]